#### Contact

coreykukowski@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/corey-kukowski-56063a6 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

ICU

**Critical Care** 

Medical/Surgical

### Languages

English

### Honors-Awards

Volunteer 20 year Appreciation Award

# Corey Kukowski

Critical Care Response Nurse at Stanford Medical Center San Francisco

## Summary

Critical Care Response Nurse assisting inpatient nursing staff with medically challenging patients as well as responding to Code Blue calls, RRT pages, Stroke codes, Sepsis alerts, difficult IV starts and feeding tube placements. Continue to work with the medical, surgical, neurosurgical and trauma ICU, now assist with CV ICU and ER/ED as well. Served as the Stanford Health Care Shared Leadership Coordinating Council Chair-elect for 2 years.

Specialties: CCRN, ACLS, preceptor, mentor, equipment committee and Cortrak super-user lead as well as provide in services for new staff on equipment used in the ICU, train and provide update for Cortrak super-user group, and provide classes on hemodynamics to new critical care nurses.

## Experience

Stanford Health Care
Critical Care Response Nurse
July 2011 - Present (9 years 2 months)
Palo Alto, CA

Critical Care Response Nurse's respond to all Code Blue, RRT, Code Sepsis and Stroke Code alerts as well as assist inpatient nursing staff with medically challenging patients. Continue to help out in the mixed trauma, medical, surgical and neuro intensive care unit as well as cardio-thoracic ICU as needed. Multiple leadership opportunities that I have tackled include SHC Shared Leadership Coordinating Council Chair-elect, Preceptor and Mentor as well as manage the Cortrak Electromagnetically Guided Placement Device Program and serve as The Hospital Lead Cortrak Super user. Trained as CRRT super user, member of SICU and FASST Champion groups and all around Guru. Provide bedside education to nurses and staff about new and current equipment training, electronic health record updates and classes on hemodynamics to new critical care nurse trainees.

Novasyte LLC

Clinical Consultant for Avanos/Cortrak Enteral Access System April 2013 - Present (7 years 5 months)

Nationwide

Trained as clinical support for bedside placement of the Cortrak Enteral Access System. Provide support and training for clinical nurse both at the bedside and in the classroom setting that are contemplating or currently utilizing the Cortrak system.

American Mobile Healthcare
Critical Care Registered Nurse
November 2007 - July 2011 (3 years 9 months)

Critical Care Nurse worked in multiple settings from 25 beds to 500+ bed facilities. Intensive Care Units included medical/surgical, neurosurgical, trauma and cardiac. Also floated and provided support for emergency department, step down, telemetry and recovery. Hospitals included Scripps La Jolla, Sharp Medical Center, University of California, San Francisco, Penrose Medical Center and Stanford Medical Center.

Air National Guard/ US Army

Critical Care Nurse/First Sergeant/Aeromedical Technician/Patriot Missle System Operator (Army)

January 1985 - July 2009 (24 years 7 months)

Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area/Fresno Ca/El Paso, Tx and Giessen West Germany

Critical Care Air Transport nurse tasked to pick up wounded and sick military members during time of war and peace. Infection Control Officer, oversaw all aspects of infection control during peace time and assist with implementation during periods of conflict. Deployed to Afghanistan in Fall 2008 to spring 2009 as part of 3 person Critical Care Air Transport team to manage the care for critically wounded and sick military members and combatants. U.S. Army 1985-1989 Patriot Missile System Operator and Mechanic. Button pusher, card swapper, HMMTT driver, radio operator and missile launcher. Retired from military service with 21 (qualifying) years of service, in 2009.

## Education

San Francisco State University BSN, Nursing · (1999 - 2001)

## Fresno City College

Associate of Science (AS), General Studies · (1991 - 1993)